

Fort Lauderdale, FL 954.907.2097 <u>albertdburks@gmail.com</u> /in/albertdburks/ <u>albertburks.github.io/portfolio</u>

About

Passionate Product Designer with 8+ years of experience in the application of the complete design process, from concept to final delivery. I look at anything I design as an extension and reflection of myself so creating the best possible product is my ultimate goal.

Technical

Figma InVision Github

Photoshop Maze Visual Studio

InDesign Marvel Code

Illustrator Miro Webflow

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Product Designer | Shift4Shop

DECEMBER 2014 - PRESENT

- Responsible for the internal styleguide and implementation of design systems for our marketing material, templates and client platform.
- Create wireframes and prototypes which help to demonstrate UX design principles, as well as define and drive project vision.
- Work collaboratively with UX engineering and product management teams to produce high quality work informed by research and validation processes.
- Have designed 80+ of high fidelity industry-specific eCommerce themes that provide products and services online.
- Within a 2-month time frame helped complete the company's rebranding which resulted in a campaign during Super Bowl 2021 seen by an audience of over 100 million.

Web Designer | DAS Group

JULY 2012 - AUGUST 2014

- · Worked collaboratively with agency leaders to design and build websites for a variety of different markets.
- Helped to conceptualize and executive the design deliverables for a numerous ad campaigns seen across the internet.

Project Manager | Top of Google

MARCH 2011 - MAY 2012

- Oversaw the day to day operations of over 30 websites, acting as webmaster to keep content and search engine optimization up-to-date.
- Provided creative direction on refreshing the look and feel of business branding, as well as designing multiple landing pages for existing clients.

EDUCATION

Ironhack Miami | Part-time UX/UI Bootcamp Projects

- Unravel Used UX methodologies such as competitive analysis, market research and desirability testing to deliver a prototype of an online magazine catering to the interests of our chosen persona, the mindfulness focused millenial.
- Ev'ry Using quantitative data and comprehensive analysis of competitor products we prototyped of an app focused on how to leverage technology to help the black community live a more positive and affirming life.
- APEX A scheduling and management app designed for a sports agency to help their clients make better use of their time and make access to necessary resources more readily available.

ITT Technical Institute | AA in Visual Communications